麦考伊：企业号医疗日志，星历 5027.3。
McCOY: Enterprise Medical Log, stardate 5027.3.
伦纳德·麦考伊医生记录。
Dr. Leonard McCoy recording.
我很担心柯克舰长。
I'm concerned about Captain Kirk.
他表现出越来越紧张和情绪压力的迹象。
He shows indications of increasing tension and emotional stress.
我完成了任务，舰长。
I have completed the assignment, captain.
- 理论上的入侵-- - 是的，契科夫先生。我会读。
- A theoretical incursion into-- - Yes, Mr. Chekov. I can read.
和往常一样，你的理论评估与我的不一致。
And as usual, your theoretical evaluations do not tally with mine.
回到你的岗位，你的工作令人满意时我会通知你。
Return to your duty and I'll let you know when your work is satisfactory.
史波克，请对该区域进行全传感器扫描。
Spock, full-sensor scan of the region, please.
- 我确实对它做了一份完整的报告-- - 是的，那是过去。
- I did give a full report on it-- - Yes, that was the past.
我关心的是现在。
I'm concerned with the present.
向我展示当前的信息
Or is it becoming too much for this crew
对船员来说这很过分吗？
to present me with current information?
不，先生。合规性没有问题。
No, sir. Compliance presents no problem.
那么，史波克先生，请遵守。
Then, Mr. Spock, comply.
传感器扫描到二分之一秒差距。
Sensor scan to one-half parsec.
- 没问题，舰长。 - 很好。
- Negative, captain. - Very well.
麦考伊：我找不到舰长行为的理由
McCOY: I can find no reason for the captain's behavior
除了，可能，我们已经巡逻太久了
except, possibly, that we've been on patrol too long
没有换班和消遣。
without relief and diversion.
他拒绝了我对他进行心理分析的所有尝试。
He has resisted all my attempts to run a psychological profile on him.
保持航向和速度，长官。
Maintaining course and speed, sir.
改变航线，转到185标记3。
Change course. Come about to 185 mark 3.
但这将导致我们直接进入罗慕伦中立区。
But that will lead us directly into the Romulan Neutral Zone.
苏鲁先生，这很有洞察力。
That's very perceptive, Mr. Sulu.
我知道航线变化会把我们带到哪里。
I know where the course change takes us.
- 执行。 - 是，长官。
- Execute. - Aye, sir.
将传感器扫描增加到一秒差距。
Increasing sensor scan to one parsec.
所有的扫描仪报告没有异常，我们附近没有任何异常。
All scanners report clear and nothing in our immediate vicinity.
越来越好了，史波克先生。
Better and better, Mr. Spock.
舰长，正在离开中立区，
Captain, leaving neutral zone,
现在进入罗慕伦空间。
now entering Romulan space.
很好，苏鲁先生。
Very well, Mister Sulu.
上尉。
Lieutenant.
命令是什么时候下达的？
When did the order come through?
- 命令？ - 来自星际舰队。
- Order? - From Starfleet.
进入中立区的命令。
The order to enter the neutral zone.
我不知道有什么命令，斯科特先生。
There's been no order I know of, Mr. Scott.
但肯定的是，舰长没有权利这样做吧？
But surely the captain couldn't be doing this on his own authority?
如果你们两个有任何抱怨，你可以把它们公开。
If you two have any complaints, you can bring them out into the open.
那是一艘克林贡飞船。
That's a Klingon ship.
但它不可能，在这个领域不可能。
But it couldn't be, not in this area.
情报报告罗慕伦人现在使用克林贡设计。
Intelligence reports Romulans now using Klingon design.
拉红色警报，进入战斗岗位，相位炮待命。
Sound red alert, man battle stations. Stand by main phasers.
战斗岗位，所有人，战斗岗位。
Battle stations, all hands, battle stations.
[警报声]
[ALARM BLARING]
第二艘船出现了。
A second ship has appeared.
更正。现在有三艘。
Correction. There are now three.
我们被包围了。
We are surrounded.
柯克：宇宙，最后的边疆
KIRK: Space, the final frontier.
这些是星舰企业号的航程。
These are the voyages of the starship Enterprise.
它的五年任务：探索未知的新世界，
Its five-year mission: To explore strange new worlds,
寻找新生命和新文明，
to seek out new life and new civilizations,
勇踏前人未至之境。
to boldly go where no man has gone before.
乌乎拉上尉，给星际舰队司令部发一条加密信息。
Lieutenant Uhura, code a message to Starfleet Command.
将我们的情况告知他们，包括到现在为止的所有日志条目。
Advise them of our situation, include all log entries to this point.
是的，长官。
Aye, aye, sir.
史波克先生，你的传感器读数清晰。发生了什么？
Mr. Spock, your sensors read clear. What happened?
- 我有一个理论，舰长-- - 乌乎拉：柯克舰长。
- I have a theory, captain-- - UHURA: Captain Kirk.
我正在从罗慕伦船只接收 2 级信号。
I'm receiving Class 2 signal from the Romulan vessel.
把它放在屏幕上，上尉，
Put it on the viewing screen, lieutenant,
并完成发给星际舰队司令部的消息。
and complete that message to Starfleet Command.
你已被确认为星舰企业号。
You have been identified as the starship Enterprise.
詹姆斯·T·柯克舰长，已知是指挥。
Captain James T. Kirk, last known to be in command.
你的信息是正确的。我是柯克舰长。
Your information is correct. This is Captain Kirk.
我是罗慕伦舰队的副指挥官塔尔。
I am Sub-Commander Tal of the Romulan fleet.
你的船被包围了，舰长。
Your ship is surrounded, captain.
请你立即投降，否则我们会摧毁你。
You will surrender immediately or we will destroy you.
上尉。
Lieutenant.
他们想要什么东西，
They want something,
否则他们早就把我们消灭了。
or they would have destroyed us by now.
没错，舰长。那是标准的罗慕伦程序。
True, captain. That would be standard Romulan procedure.
他们要的是我的飞船。而且非常想要。
It's my ship they want. And very badly.
它将是一个很好的战利品。
It would be a great prize.
上尉。
Lieutenant.
省省你的威胁吧。
Save your threats.
如果你登上这艘船，我就炸了它。你将一无所获。
If you board this ship, I'll blow it up. You'll gain nothing.
- 你旁边的是谁？ - 我的大副，史波克上校。
- Who is that beside you? - My first officer, Commander Spock.
瓦肯人。
Vulcan.
[对讲机哔哔声]
[INTERCOM BEEPS]
是的，指挥官。
Yes, commander.
任何人都不应该这么快就决定去死，舰长。
No one should decide quickly to die, captain.
我们给你一个小时。
We give you one of your hours.
如果时间到了不交出你的船，
If you do not surrender your ship at the end of that time,
你的毁灭是必然的。
your destruction is certain.
如果你想，我们乐意交流。
We will be open to communication, should you wish it.
你要明白星际舰队司令部
You understand that Starfleet Command
已被告知情况。
has been advised of the situation.
一条子空间消息需要三周时间才能到达星际舰队。
A sub-space message will take three weeks to reach Starfleet.
决定权在你，舰长。一小时。
The decision is yours, captain. One hour.
柯克：这艘船的设计是一样的。
KIRK: The design of the ship is the same.
史波克先生，
Mr. Spock,
你说你有一个理论，为什么你的传感器
you said you had a theory on why your sensors
在新船到达我们面前时才检测到它们？
didn't pick up the new ships until they were upon us?
我相信罗慕伦人已经开发出一种隐形装置
I believe the Romulans have developed a cloaking device
这使我们的跟踪传感器失效。
which renders our tracking sensors useless.
如果是这样，罗慕伦人可以攻击联邦领域
If so, the Romulans could attack into Federation territory
在我们知道他们在那里之前，甚至在一艘船
before we knew they were there, before a vessel
或者一个星球开始建立防线前。
or a planet could even begin to get their defenses up.
他们抓住了我们，没错。
They caught us, right enough.
这是一个绝妙的观察，斯科特先生。你还有其他有用的意见吗？
That's a brilliant observation, Mr. Scott. Do you have other helpful opinions?
- 好吧，我们没有太多选择。 - 我们有三个。
- Well, we've not got many choices. - We have three.
我们可以战斗然后被摧毁。
We can fight and be destroyed.
或者我们可以自己摧毁企业号
Or we can destroy the Enterprise ourselves
让她远离罗慕伦人，或者我们可以……
and keep her from the Romulans, or we can...
...投降。
...surrender.
先生们，意见？
Opinions, gentlemen?
如果企业号被罗慕伦人夺取
If the Enterprise is taken by the Romulans
他们会知道关于星舰的一切。
they'll know everything there is to know about a starship.
如果我们没有遵守你的命令穿过中立区
If we had not crossed the neutral zone on your order
你现在就不需要我们的意见来支持决定
you would not now need our opinions to support a decision
这本不该发生。
which should never have had to be made.
吉姆，你命令我们？
Jim, you ordered us?
你没有权限。
You had no authority.
- 解散，医生。 - 吉姆。
- Dismissed, doctor. - Jim.
我说解散。
I said dismissed.
[对讲机铃声]
[INTERCOM CHIMES]
乌乎拉 [通过对讲机]：舰桥呼叫柯克舰长。
UHURA [OVER INTERCOM]: Bridge to Captain Kirk.
我是柯克
Kirk here.
罗慕伦船只再次发出信号，长官。
The Romulan vessel is signaling again, sir.
- 将它们放在屏幕上。 - 乌乎拉：是的，长官。
- Put them on the screen. - UHURA: Aye, aye, sir.
我的指挥官想和你谈谈，柯克舰长。
My commander wishes to speak with you, Captain Kirk.
接通他
Put him on.
指挥官想见你
The commander wishes to see you
和你在这艘船上的大副。
and your first officer aboard this vessel.
感觉这个问题需要讨论。
It is felt this matter requires discussion.
为什么我们要自投罗网？
Why should we walk right into your hands?
我的两名军官将传送上你的船
Two of my officers will beam aboard your vessel
作为交换人质。
as exchanged hostages while you are here.
我们有什么保证他们会登上我们的船
What guarantee do we have that they'll beam aboard our ship
一旦我们上了你的船？
once we're on yours?
诚然，我们不会轻易信任对方，舰长。
Granted, we do not easily trust each other, captain.
但你们是侵犯我们领土的人。
But you are the ones who violated our territory.
不应该是我们不信任你的动机吗？
Should it not be we who distrust your motives?
但是，我们同意同时交换。
However, we agree to simultaneous exchange.
给我们你的传送坐标。我们正在传送上船。
Give us your transporter coordinates. We're beaming aboard.
最后一个命令，工程师斯科特。如果我们不回来，
One final order, Engineer Scott. If we do not return,
一定不能让企业号被夺走。
the Enterprise must not be taken.
如果罗慕伦人试图这样做，你要战斗，如果有必要的话
If the Romulans attempt it, you're to fight and if necessary
自毁，明白吗？
destroy yourselves, is that clear?
非常明白。
Perfectly clear.
启动。
Energize.
柯克舰长。
Captain Kirk.
指挥官，我很荣幸。
Commander, I'm honored.
我不这么认为。
I don't think so.
但是我们有一件重要的事情要讨论。
But we have an important matter to discuss.
你表面上的礼貌是讨论的序曲。
And your superficial courtesies are an overture to that discussion.
你就是大副。
You are the first officer.
史波克。
Spock.
我先和舰长说话。
I speak first with the captain.
你可以在外面等。
You may wait outside.
侵入罗慕伦空间的事情是银河系的重要事件之一，
The matter of trespass into Romulan space is one of galactic import,
违反了条约。
a violation of treaties.
现在，我简单地问你，
Now, I ask you simply,
你在这里的使命是什么？
what is your mission here?
仪器故障导致导航错误。
Instrument failure caused navigational error.
在我们意识到之前，我们已经穿过了中立区。
We were across the neutral zone before we realized it.
我们还没来得及回来就被你们的船包围了。
We were surrounded by your ships before we could get back.
一艘星舰，
A starship,
星际舰队最好的船只之一。
one of the Starfleet's finest vessels.
你是说仪器故障正如你说的那样根本没有引起注意
You are saying instrument failure as radical as you suggest went unnoticed
直到你完全穿过中立区？
until you were well past the neutral zone?
可能会发生事故，断电、备用系统可能会出现故障。
Accidents can happen, cut-off, back-up systems can malfunction.
我们几个月前就该进行全面检修了。
We were due for an overhaul months ago.
我知道了。
I see.
但是你能在有故障时导航？
But you were able to navigate with this malfunction?
错误已得到纠正。
The error was corrected.
但我怀疑这是否能排除你的间谍嫌疑。
But I doubt if it will clear you of espionage.
我们不是在当间谍，指挥官。
We were not spying, commander.
你的语言对我来说一直是最难的，舰长。
Your language has always been most difficult for me, captain.
也许你有另一种说法？
Perhaps you have another word for it?
如果你认为我们在那里，那你就大错特错了--
You are grossly mistaken if you think that we were there--
- 你听我说-- - 如果是罗慕伦船只
- You listen to me-- - If a Romulan vessel
没有很好的解释就冒险深入联邦领域，
ventured far into Federation territory without good explanation,
星际基地指挥官会做什么？
what would a starbase commander do?
你看，
You see,
它是双向的。
it works both ways.
我几乎不相信你是受害方。
I hardly believe you are the injured party.
史波克。
Spock.
进来吧。
Come in.
舰长发表了声明。
The captain has made his statement.
我明白。
I understand.
我必须承认
I must admit
见到你有点惊喜，史波克。
some surprise on seeing you, Spock.
我们不知道企业号上有瓦肯人。
We were not aware of Vulcans aboard the Enterprise.
星际舰队没有习惯
Starfleet is not in the habit
告知罗慕伦人其舰只的人员情况。
of informing Romulans of its ships' personnel.
的确。
Quite so.
然而有一些船，
Yet there are certain ships,
一些我们认识的官员。
certain officers that are known to us.
你的情况看起来最有趣。
Your situation appears most interesting.
是什么让你对史巴克特别感兴趣？
What earns Spock your special interest?
他是个瓦肯人。
He is a Vulcan.
我们的祖先有着相同的根源
Our forebears had the same roots
和起源，你不会明白的，舰长。
and origins, something you wouldn't understand, captain.
我们能感应瓦肯人，
We can appreciate the Vulcans,
我们远方的兄弟。
our distant brothers.
我听说过瓦肯诚实
I have heard of Vulcan integrity
和个人荣誉。
and personal honor.
有个著名说法，
There is a well-known saying,
抑或是谣传，
or is it a myth,
瓦肯人不会说谎。
that Vulcans are incapable of lying.
这不是谣传。
It is no myth.
那么现在就如实告诉我，
Then tell me truthfully now,
以你作为瓦肯人的荣誉，你们的任务是什么？
by your honor as a Vulcan, what was your mission?
我保留发言权
I reserve the privilege of speaking
只有当它不会侵犯我作为瓦肯人的荣誉时。
only when it will not violate my honor as a Vulcan.
一个瓦肯人不值得诉诸诡计。
It is unworthy of a Vulcan to resort to subterfuge.
你很聪明，指挥官。
You're being clever, commander.
这是罗慕伦人所不配的。
That is unworthy of a Romulan.
对自己隐瞒真相并不是谎言。
It is not a lie to keep the truth to oneself.
那么这里有一个真相
Then there is a truth here
仍然没有说出来。
that remains unspoken.
都告诉你了，没什么好说的。
You've been told everything, there's nothing else to say.
这是史波克先生不肯透露的真相。
There is Mr. Spock's unspoken truth.
你知道我们开发的隐形装置。
You knew of the cloaking device that we have developed.
你故意侵犯罗慕伦空间
You deliberately violated Romulan space
根据联邦司令部的命令公然执行间谍任务。
with a blatant spy mission by order of the Federation Command.
- 我们都经历过。 - 我们甚至还没有开始。
- We've been all through that. - We have not even begun.
我没有能用的手段
There is no force that I can use
来让一个瓦肯人说话。
on a Vulcan that will make him speak.
这是事实。
That is a fact.
但是有罗慕伦人的方法
But there are Romulan methods
对人类和人类弱点
completely effective against humans
完全有效。
and human weaknesses.
你不会求助于他们，指挥官。
You would not resort to them, commander.
他们将证明对舰长无效。
They would prove ineffective against the captain.
然后他们会让他死，
Then they will leave him dead,
或者比死更糟糕的事情。
or what might be worse than dead.
但我会知道你不肯透露的真相。
But I will know your unspoken truths.
让她骂。没什么好说的。
Let her rant. There's nothing to say.
我不能让船长被进一步摧毁。
I cannot allow the captain to be further destroyed.
指挥的压力给他带来了沉重的负担。
The strain of command has worn heavily upon him.
- 他这几周都不像他自己了。 - 骗人。
- He's not been himself for weeks. - That's a lie.
如你所见，柯克舰长是一个非常敏感和情绪化的人。
As you can see, Captain Kirk is a highly sensitive and emotional person.
我相信他已经失去了理性决策的能力。
I believe he has lost the capacity for rational decision.
- 闭嘴，史波克。 - 我没有泄露任何秘密。
- Shut up, Spock. - I am betraying no secrets.
指挥官怀疑是星际舰队命令
The commander's suspicion that Starfleet ordered
企业号进入中立区的，这是不可接受的。
the Enterprise into the neutral zone is unacceptable.
我们的快速捕获证明了它的鲁莽。
Our rapid capture demonstrates its foolhardiness.
你这个肮脏的骗子。
You filthy liar.
我说的是实话
I am speaking the truth
为了企业号和联邦的利益。
for the benefit of the Enterprise and the Federation.
我说现在并记录在案
I say now and for the record
柯克舰长命令企业号穿越中立区
that Captain Kirk ordered the Enterprise across the neutral zone
靠他自己的主动性和他对荣耀的渴望。
on his own initiative and his craving for glory.
我会为此杀了你，你这个叛徒，我会杀了你。
I'll kill you for this, you traitor, I'll kill you.
我会杀了你。
I'll kill you.
他不理智。
He is not sane.
注意，企业号。我在罗慕伦旗舰上和你们讲话。
Attention, Enterprise. I am speaking to you from the Romulan flagship.
联邦星舰企业号，由詹姆斯·T·柯克舰长指挥
The USS Enterprise, under command of Captain James T. Kirk
正式被指控犯有间谍罪。
is formally charged with espionage.
大副史波克的证词
The testimony of First Officer Spock
非常有助于确认
was highly instrumental in confirming
这次闯入罗慕伦领域并非偶然。
this intrusion into Romulan space was not an accident.
大副史波克的证词很具体
First Officer Spock's testimony was specific
你的船没有受星际舰队司令部或联邦委员会的命令
that your ship was not under orders from Starfleet Command
执行这样的间谍任务。
or the Federation Council to perform such a spy mission.
全权负责的是柯克舰长。
It was Captain Kirk who was solely responsible.
由于船员们不得不服从命令，
Since the crew had no choice but to obey orders,
船员将不承担任何责任。
the crew will not be held responsible.
因此，我命令工程师斯科特，
Therefore, I am ordering Engineer Scott,
目前指挥企业号，
presently in command of the Enterprise,
跟随罗慕伦旗舰
to follow the Romulan flagship
到我们的大本营。
to our home base.
你将在那里接受处理并释放到联邦指挥部。
You will there be processed and released to Federation Command.
在判决通过之前，柯克舰长将被监禁。
Until judgment is passed, Captain Kirk will be held in confinement.
保安。把我们的两个罗慕伦人质关禁闭。
Security. Put our two Romulan hostages in the brig.
乌乎拉上尉，帮我接通那艘船。
Lieutenant Uhura, give me a channel to that ship.
频道开放了，斯科特先生，你被接入了。
Channel is open, Mr. Scott, and you are tied in.
这是斯科特少校。
This is Lieutenant Commander Scott.
企业号只接受柯克舰长的命令。
The Enterprise takes no orders except those of Captain Kirk.
我们会一直待在这里，直到他回来。
And we will stay right here until he returns.
如果你试图登上或征用企业号，
And if you make any attempt to board or commandeer the Enterprise,
我们将尽可能地将你们和飞船一起炸成碎片。
it will be blown to bits along with as many of you as we can take with us.
你们人类发出了勇敢的声音。
You humans make a brave noise.
有很多方法可以让你相信自己的错误。
There are ways to convince you of your errors.
你听到了吗，胆小鬼？
Did you hear that, you coward?
你背叛了你所知道的一切有价值的东西。
You've betrayed everything of value you ever knew.
你听到人类正直的声音了吗？
Did you hear the sound of human integrity?
带他去保安室。
Take him to the security room.
人类中的瓦肯人，
A Vulcan among humans,
与他们一起生活、工作。
living, working with them.
我本以为这种情况会让你无法忍受。
I would think the situation would be intolerable to you.
我是半个瓦肯人。我妈妈是人类。
I am half-Vulcan. My mother is a human.
那你效忠于谁呢？
To whom is your allegiance then?
你称自己为地球人还是瓦肯人？
Do you call yourself Terran or Vulcan?
瓦肯人。
Vulcan.
你当星际舰队军官多久了，史波克？
How long have you been a Starfleet officer, Spock?
- 十八年。 - 你为柯克舰长服务。
- Eighteen years. - And you serve Captain Kirk.
你喜欢他吗？你喜欢你的船员吗？
Do you like him? Do you like your shipmates?
- 这个问题无关紧要。 - 可能。
- The question is irrelevant. - Possibly.
但你服从柯克舰长的命令，甚至服从于他的一时兴起。
But you are subordinate to Captain Kirk's orders, even to his whims.
作为一名军官，我的职责是服从他。
My duty as an officer is to obey him.
你是个更优秀的人。
You are a superior being.
为什么不指挥？
Why do you not command?
我不想要一艘我自己的船。
I do not desire a ship of my own.
还是说没有人给你这个瓦肯人提供这种机会？
Or is it that no one has offered you, a Vulcan, that opportunity?
这样的机会极为罕见。
Such opportunities are extremely rare.
对于有你能力和成就的人，
For someone with your capabilities and accomplishments,
机会来了。
opportunities are made.
将来也是。
And will be.
如果你不再把联邦看成是整个宇宙，
I will see to that if you will stop looking on the Federation
我就会看到这一点。
as the whole universe.
不是的，你知道的。
It is not, you know.
这个想法偶尔会在我脑海中闪过。
That thought has occasionally crossed my mind.
你必须有自己的船。
You must have your own ship.
指挥官，我们说清楚好吗？
Commander, shall we speak plainly?
是你迫切需要一艘船。
It is you who desperately need a ship.
你想要企业号。
You want the Enterprise.
当然。
Of course.
将企业号完好无损地带回家对我来说将是一项了不起的成就。
It would be a great achievement for me to bring home the Enterprise intact.
这将大大拓宽我的权力范围。
It would broaden the scope of my powers greatly.
这将是一生的成就。
It would be the achievement of a lifetime.
它将为你提供平等的机会。
And it would open equal opportunities for you.
[尖叫]
[SCREAMS]
乌乎拉 [通过对讲机]：舰桥呼叫麦考伊医生。
UHURA [OVER INTERCOM]: Bridge to Dr. McCoy.
- 我是麦考伊。 - 医生，你必须立即登船
- McCoy here. - Doctor, you must beam aboard
罗慕伦旗舰有人受伤了。
the Romulan flagship immediately. There's been an injury.
- 我不上门服务。 - 医生，我是柯克舰长。
- I don't make house calls. - Doctor, it's Captain Kirk.
他会康复，但需要进一步关注。
He'll recover, but he'll need further attention.
通知你的上级。
Inform your superior.
[对讲机哔哔声]
[INTERCOM BEEPS]
什么事？
Yes?
我会来的。
I'll come there.
跟我来。
Attend me.
我忘了说，我希望你来吃晚饭。
I neglected to mention, I'll expect you for dinner.
我们有很多事情要讨论。
We have much to discuss.
是吗？
Indeed?
请允许我重新表述。
Allow me to rephrase.
你能和我一起吃晚饭吗？
Will you join me for dinner?
我很荣幸，指挥官。
I am honored, commander.
守卫也请来了？
Are the guards also invited?
史波克先生。
Mr. Spock.
除了忠诚的罗慕伦人，这条走廊是禁止进入的。
That corridor is forbidden to all but loyal Romulans.
当然。我会服从你的限制。
Of course. I shall obey your restrictions.
我希望有一天
I hope that one day
你无需遵守任何限制。
there will be no need for you to observe any restrictions.
这将是不合逻辑的
It would be illogical
假设所有条件保持稳定。
to assume that all conditions remain stable.
- 你是医生吗？ - 麦考伊。
- Are you the doctor? - McCoy.
首席医疗官。
Chief medical officer.
柯克舰长的情况？
Captain Kirk's condition?
嗯，你可以自己看看。
Well, you can see for yourself.
他精神抑郁，身体虚弱，
He's mentally depressed, physically weak,
迷失方向，表现出迫害和反叛的感觉。
disoriented, displays feelings of persecution and rebellion.
那么按照你自己的正常标准，
Then by your own standards of normality,
这个人并不完全能胜任。
this man is not fully competent.
不能，现在不能。
No, not now.
史波克 先生表示他相信
Mr. Spock has stated that he believes
舰长没有权力或命令穿越中立区。
the captain had no authority or order to cross the neutral zone.
早先是不是这种精神上的无能在困扰着他？
Could this mental incapacity have afflicted him earlier?
是的，这是可能的。
Yes, it's possible.
史波克先生，
Mr. Spock,
医生现在已经证实了你的证词。
the doctor has now confirmed your testimony.
至于你们舰长的精神状态，
As to the mental state of your captain,
他过去和现在都不适合继续指挥企业号。
he was and is unfit to continue in command of the Enterprise.
现在这个责任落在了你身上。
That duty has now fallen on you.
你准备好行使这个功能了吗？
Are you ready to exercise that function?
- 我已经准备好了。 - 史波克，我不相信。
- I am ready. - Spock, I don't believe it.
你付不起让他出卖自己的代价。
There's no price you could pay that would make him sell out.
此事不公开讨论，医生。
The matter is not open for discussion, doctor.
- 你的意思是这件事是--？ - 够了，医生。
- What do you mean the matter is--? - That's enough, doctor.
作为医生，你的职责是挽救生命。
As a physician, your duty is to save lives.
史波克先生的职责是领导企业号
Mr. Spock's duty is to lead the Enterprise
和它的船员到一个安全的避风港。
and its crew to a safe haven.
别无选择，医生。
There is no alternative, doctor.
船员的安全现在是最重要的问题。
The safety of the crew is now the paramount issue.
再抵制下去就是误导性的忠诚了。
It is misguided loyalty to resist any further.
你这个叛徒
You traitor.
我会杀了你。
I'll kill you.
[柯克咕噜声]
[KIRK GRUNTS]
你做了什么？
What did you do?
我对他的攻击毫无准备。
I was unprepared for his attack.
我本能地使用了瓦肯死亡之握。
I instinctively used the Vulcan death grip.
你的直觉还是不错的，史波克先生。
Your instincts are still good, Mr. Spock.
舰长死了。
The captain is dead.
医生！麦考伊医生！
Doctor! Dr. McCoy!
麦考伊医生。
Dr. McCoy.
我留下了任何人不得进入这里的命令。
I left orders that no one was to come in here.
- 他活着。活着。 - 好吧，既然你知道了，
- He's alive. Alive. - Well, now that you know it,
你不妨帮帮我。把生理刺激器递给我。
you might as well assist me. Hand me the physio-stimulator.
但他已经死了。他们的医生证明他已经死了。
But he was dead. Their doctors certified he was dead.
史波克对他用了神经阻断术来模拟死亡。
Spock gave him a nerve pinch to simulate death.
那么史波克先生不是叛徒。
Then Mr. Spock isn't a traitor.
而你一直都知道，但你没有--
And you knew that all the time and you didn't--
我登上罗慕伦飞船时才知道。
I didn't know it until I beamed aboard the Romulan ship.
吉姆和史波克是在联邦的命令下行动的。
Jim and Spock were operating under Federation orders.
[柯克呻吟]
[KIRK GROANING]
我的脖子感觉像是被扭断了。
My neck feels like it's been twisted off.
这是给你的瓦肯死亡之握。
That's the Vulcan death grip for you.
没有瓦肯死亡之握这样的东西。
There's no such thing as a Vulcan death grip.
哦，但罗慕伦人不知道这一点。
Oh, but the Romulans don't know that.
确实骗过了医生们。
Sure fooled the doctors.
你冒了很大的风险，他们没有开始尸检。
You took a big chance that they didn't start an autopsy.
至于其他船员，我还是死了。
As far as the rest of crew is concerned, I'm still dead.
为什么？
Why?
这就是整个化妆舞会的目的。
That's what this whole masquerade was about.
让企业号和联盟摆脱困境。
To keep the Enterprise and the Federation off the hook.
因此，如果出现任何问题
So that if any thing went wrong
你会受到指责。
you would be the one to blame.
老骨头，
Bones,
我要你为手术做准备。
I want you to prepare for surgery.
做什么的？
What for?
麦考伊 [通过对讲机]：医务室呼叫舰桥。
McCOY [OVER INTERCOM]: Sickbay to bridge.
我是斯科特，医生。
Scott here, doctor.
斯科特先生，你能到医务室报告吗？
Mr. Scott, will you report to Sickbay?
医务室？这种时候我不能离开舰桥。
Sickbay? I can't leave the bridge at a time like this.
你必须来，这事很紧急。
You have to, it's urgent.
我们被准备攻击我们的敌舰包围，
We're surrounded by enemy vessels ready to attack us,
我不知道还有什么比这更紧急。
I don't know of anything more urgent than that.
我知道。
Well, I do.
斯科特先生，拜托。
Mr. Scott, please.
好的，医生。
All right, doctor.
最好是重要的事。斯科特完毕。
It better be important. Scott out.
好的，医生，什么事这么紧急--？
All right, doctor, what's so urgent that--?
舰长。
Captain.
柯克舰长。
Captain Kirk.
是的。
Yes.
好吧，你自己看起来就像是魔鬼，不过你是活的。
Well, you look like the devil himself, but as long as you're alive.
这到底是怎么回事？
What's it all about?
那些罗慕伦军官还在船上吗？
Are those Romulan officers still aboard the ship?
他们在禁闭室，长官。
They're in the brig, sir.
我需要一件罗慕伦制服。
I'll need a Romulan uniform.
是的，我很乐意。
Aye. It'll be a pleasure.
[门打开和关闭]
[DOORS OPEN AND CLOSE]
指挥官：我为你准备了特别的瓦肯菜肴。
COMMANDER: I've had special Vulcan dishes prepared for you.
我希望它们是你喜欢的。
I hope they're to your liking.
我很受宠若惊，指挥官。
I'm very flattered, commander.
毫无疑问，你船上的美食
There is no doubt that the cuisine aboard your vessel
远优于企业号。
is far superior to that of the Enterprise.
这确实有非常强大的招聘吸引力。
It is, indeed, a very powerful recruiting inducement.
我们还有其他奖励。
We have other inducements.
史波克到底在干什么？
What the devil is Spock doing?
是什么耽误了他？
What's delaying him?
我希望我知道。
I wish I knew.
斯科提，你确定我们和史波克的通讯畅通吗？
Scotty, are you sure we have a clear channel to Spock?
是的，长官。毫无疑问。
Aye, sir. No doubt of it.
那我们不能再等了。准备好让我登上旗舰。
Then we can't wait any longer. Prepare to beam me aboard the flagship.
斯科提：但是史波克先生还没有设置正确的坐标。
SCOTTY: But Mr. Spock hasn't set the proper coordinates yet.
- 没办法，斯科提。 - 你冒着很大的风险，吉姆。
- Can't be helped, Scotty. - You're taking an awful chance, Jim.
只要别把我放到舱壁里，传送。
Just don't put me inside a bulkhead. Energize.
百夫长，对不起，不允许任何人--
Centurion, I'm sorry, no one is allowed--
我刚刚成功逃离了联邦船只。
I have just effected an escape from the Federation vessel.
我有给塔尔副指挥官的信息。他在哪里？
I have information for Sub-Commander Tal. Where is he?
他在控制中心，百夫长。
He's in control central, centurion.
好的。我会向他提及你的警觉性。回到你的岗位。
Good. I shall mention your alertness to him. Return to your duty.
谢谢你，百夫长。
Thank you, centurion.
你在星际舰队一无所有
You have nothing in Starfleet
无家可归。
to which to return.
我给--
I off--
我们给你提供一个选择
We offer you an alternative.
我们会为你找到一个地方，
We will find a place for you,
如果你愿意的话。
if you wish it.
一个地方？
A place?
与我一起。
With me.
罗慕伦女性不像瓦肯女性。
Romulan women are not like Vulcan females.
我们不致力于...
We are not dedicated to...
...纯逻辑
...pure logic
和冷漠无情。
and the sterility of non-emotion.
我们的人民是战士，
Our people are warriors,
通常是野蛮人。
often savage.
但我们还有许多其他令人愉快的事情。
But we are also many other pleasant things.
我没注意到罗慕伦社会的这一方面。
I was not aware of that aspect of Romulan society.
作为瓦肯人，你会研究它。
As a Vulcan, you would study it.
作为一个人类，你会找到欣赏它的方法。
As a human, you would find ways to appreciate it.
请相信我，
Please believe me,
我确实...
I do...
……欣赏它。
...appreciate it.
我很高兴。
I am so glad.
现在，完成这一场合的最后一步。
Now, one final step to make the occasion complete.
你将带领一小队罗慕伦人登上企业号。
You will lead a small party of Romulans aboard the Enterprise.
在那里，你将获得你应有的地位
And there you will take your rightful place
作为指挥官。
as its commander.
然后你将带领飞船到罗慕伦港口，
And you will lead the ship to a Romulan port,
我的旗舰就在旁边。
with my flagship at its side.
是的，当然。
Yes, of course.
但不是现在。
But not just this moment.
一个小时后更好。
An hour from now will do even better.
会不会...
Would it not...
...指挥官？
...commander?
是的。
Yes.
是的，会的。
Yes, it will.
史波克先生。
Mr. Spock.
你知道我有名字的。
You do know I have a first name.
我开始怀疑。
I was beginning to wonder.
嗯，我知道。
Well, I do.
你想听吗？
Would you like to hear it?
[不清楚地窃窃私语]
[WHISPERS INDISTINCTLY]
多么罕见
How rare
多么美丽。
and how beautiful.
但是当被一个士兵说出来时就显得格格不入了。
But so incongruous when spoken by a soldier.
如果你给我一点时间
If you will give me a moment,
士兵会改变自己
the soldier will transform herself
变成女人。
into a woman.
- 史波克呼叫柯克舰长。 - 柯克：我是柯克。
- Spock to Captain Kirk. - KIRK: Kirk here.
舰长，你准备好传送过来了吗？
Captain, are you prepared to beam over?
我已经在船上了，史波克。你有消息吗？
I'm already on board, Spock. Do you have the information?
是的，舰长。
Yes, captain.
隐形装置位于指挥官住处附近的区域。
The cloaking device is in an area near the commander's quarters.
它受到严密保护，除授权人员外，所有人员均不得进入。
It is closely guarded and off-limits to all but authorized personnel.
你现在的位置是什么？
What is your present location?
副指挥官塔尔。
Sub-commander Tal.
我从我们的飞船内接收到外星人的信号，长官。
I'm receiving an alien transmission from within our vessel, sir.
- 外星人？你确定吗？ - 是的，副指挥官。
- Alien? Are you certain? - Yes, sub-commander.
- 我必须知道来源。 - 正在进行三角测量，先生。
- I must know the source. - Triangulating now, sir.
史波克，我去拿隐形装置。
Spock, I'll get the cloaking device.
你能回到企业号
Will you be able to get back to the Enterprise
但不引起他们注意吗？
without attracting their attention?
不知道，舰长。目前，我相当沉重--
Unknown, captain. At present, I'm rather heavily--
我的...
Is my...
...装束现在更合适了吗？
...attire now more appropriate,
史波克先生
Mr. Spock?
指挥官，你的装束不仅更合适，
Commander, your attire is not only more appropriate,
它实际能刺激我们的交流。
it should actually stimulate our conversation.
百夫长。
Centurion.
你有这个区域的许可吗？我不认识你。
Have you clearance for this area? I do not recognize you.
船上有入侵者。有人试图进入吗？
There's an intruder aboard. Has someone tried to gain entrance?
- 我必须查看你的授权，先生。 - 在那边。
- I must see your authorization, sir. - Over there.
很难相信
It's hard to believe
我能如此感动
that I could be so moved
被外星人的手触摸。
by the touch of an alien hand.
我必须承认，我也
I must confess that I, too,
很感动。
am moved emotionally.
我知道这是不合逻辑的--
I know it is illogical--
史波克先生...
Mr. Spock...
......我们不应该质疑
...we mustn't question
我们的真实感受。
what we truly feel.
接受我们之间发生的事情，
Accept what is happening between us,
就像我一样。
even as I do.
塔尔：指挥官。
TAL: Commander.
[嗡嗡声]
[BUZZING]
允许进入。
Permission to enter.
不是现在，塔尔。
Not now, Tal.
塔尔：很紧急，指挥官。
TAL: It is urgent, commander.
指挥官：进来。
COMMANDER: Enter.
指挥官。我们截获了外星人的传送。
Commander. We have intercepted an alien transmission.
指挥官：找到它的来源。
COMMANDER: Locate its source.
塔尔：找到了，指挥官。
TAL: We have, commander.
这个房间。
This room.
隐形装置。带上他。
The cloaking device. Bring him.
保持。别动。
Hold. Don't move.
你是谁？你在这里做什么？
Who are you? What are you doing in here?
船上有敌方间谍。他会去寻找隐形装置。
There's an enemy spy aboard. He'll be after the cloaking device.
放下你的武器。
Drop your weapon.
斯科提，
Scotty,
传送。
energize.
斯科提：但是，先生，史波克先生呢？
SCOTTY: But, sir, what about Mr. Spock?
希望他能给我们足够的时间来安装这个隐形装置。
Hope he can buy us enough time to get this cloaking device installed.
它必须连接到我们的偏转护盾控制上。
It'll have to be hooked into our deflector-shield control.
- 你能做到吗？ - 我不知道。
- Can you do it? - I don't know.
你有 15 分钟，斯科提。
You have 15 minutes, Scotty.
指挥官，隐形装置不见了。
Commander, the cloaking device is gone.
全面警戒。搜索所有甲板。
Full alert. Search all decks.
那将是无的，指挥官。
That will be profitless, commander.
我不相信你会找到它。
I do not believe you will find it.
你一定是疯了。
You must be mad.
我向你保证，
I assure you,
我很理智。
I am quite sane.
你为什么要这样对我？
Why would you do this to me?
你有什么资格这样做？
What are you that you could do this?
企业号的大副。
First Officer of the Enterprise.
你们目前的死刑方式是什么？
What is your present form of execution?
柯克：舰长日志，星历 5027.4。
KIRK: Captain's Log, stardate 5027.4.
斯科特上校有不到 15 分钟的时间
Commander Scott has less than 15 minutes
安装罗慕伦人的隐形装置并使其工作。
to install the Romulans' cloaking device and get it working.
我希望史波克先生能为我们争取到我们需要的时间。
I hope Mr. Spock can buy us the time we need.
- 苏鲁：舰长。 - 契科夫：你还活着。
- SULU: Captain. - CHEKOV: You're alive.
- 他们说你被杀了，长官。 - 报告太草率了。
- They said you'd been killed, sir. - The report was premature.
- 舰长，你的耳朵，发生了什么事？ - 我们稍后再讨论。
- Captain, your ears, what happened? - We'll discuss it later.
苏鲁先生，设定回家的航线。 契科夫，带上传感器。
Mr. Sulu, lay in a course for home. Chekov, take the sensors.
史波克先生仍在罗慕伦旗舰上。
Mr. Spock is still aboard the Romulan flagship.
我希望他的身体读数被精确定位和隔离。
I want his body readings pinpointed and isolated.
这不是请求，先生们。
That was not a request, gentlemen.
- 是的，长官。- 是的，长官。
- Aye, sir. - Aye, sir.
- 是的，长官。
Aye, sir.
回到你的岗位，副指挥官。
Return to your station, sub-commander.
听我的命令开始企业号的登船行动。
The boarding action on the Enterprise will begin with my command.
如果他们反抗，摧毁她。
If they resist, destroy her.
处决国家罪犯
Execution of state criminals
既痛苦又不愉快。
is both painful and unpleasant.
我相信细节是不必要的。
I believe the details are unnecessary.
处决将立即执行
The sentence will be carried out immediately after the charges
在指控被记录后。
have been recorded.
我首先要求获得声明权。
I demand the Right of Statement first.
你很了解罗慕伦的传统。
You understand Romulan tradition well.
要求通过。
The right is granted.
谢谢。
Thank you.
我不需要太多时间。
I shall not require much time.
我应该说不超过20分钟。
No more than 20 minutes, I should say.
找到你的盟友应该比这花费更少的时间
It should take less time than that to find your ally
他们偷了隐形装置。
who stole the cloaking device.
你不会孤独地死去。
You will not die alone.
记录罗慕伦的陈述权。
Recording the Romulan Right of Statement.
继续，史波克上校。
Proceed, Commander Spock.
我的罪行是蓄意破坏。我自愿承认我的罪行。
My crime is sabotage. I freely admit my guilt.
我作为星际舰队军官的誓言
The oath I swore as a Starfleet officer
既具体又具有约束力。
is both specific and binding.
只要我穿着制服，
As long as I wear the uniform,
我的职责就是保护联邦的安全。
my duty is to protect the security of the Federation.
很明显，你的新隐形设备对该安全构成了威胁。
Clearly, your new cloaking device is a threat to that security.
我履行了我的职责。
I carried out my duty.
每个人都在履行自己的职责。
Everyone carries out his duty.
你说出了显而易见的事实，史波克。
You state the obvious, Spock.
我的发言内容没有规定。
There is no regulation regarding the content of my statement.
我可以继续吗？
May I continue?
很好。你的 20 分钟快到了。
Very well. Your 20 minutes is almost up.
契科夫先生，那艘船上只有一个瓦肯人，
Mr. Chekov, there is only one Vulcan aboard that ship,
他应该很容易找到。
he should be easy enough to locate.
契科夫：罗慕伦人和瓦肯人读起来几乎一模一样。
CHEKOV: Romulans and Vulcans appear to read almost exactly alike.
只是有一点点不同--
There is just a slight difference which--
找到他了，先生。
Got him, sir.
尽快把坐标发给传送室。
Feed the coordinates to the transporter room on the double.
让他们准备听我的信号将他传送到船上。
Have them prepare to beam him aboard on my signal.
柯克舰长，斯科特先生在线上与您通话，长官。
Captain Kirk, Mr. Scott is on the intercom for you, sir.
说吧，斯科提。
Go ahead, Scotty.
我已经安装了设备。
I've got the device installed.
但如果我知道它是否能运作，保佑我
But bless me if I know if it's going to work.
这是我打过最大的赌
It's the biggest guess I've ever made.
- 准备，斯科提。 - 契科夫：长官。
- Stand by, Scotty. - CHEKOV: Sir.
传送室有坐标，可以传送了。
Transporter room has the coordinates and is ready for beaming.
传送室，传送史波克先生上船。
Transporter room, beam Mr. Spock aboard.
除了瓦肯人忠诚的历史传统外，
Beyond the historic tradition of Vulcan loyalty
还有罗慕兰人和瓦肯人联合起来的
there is also the combined Romulan-Vulcan history
服从职责的历史。
of obedience to duty.
传送室报告史波克先生上船了，指挥官。
Transporter room reports Mr. Spock aboard, sir.
还有罗慕伦指挥官。
And the Romulan commander.
- 指挥官？ - 是的，先生。
- The commander? - Aye, sir.
好的。
All right.
让他们尽快到舰桥报告。
Have them report to the bridge on the double.
苏鲁先生，带我们离开罗慕伦人的地方。
Mr. Sulu, take us away from the Romulans.
曲速9。
Warp factor 9.
副指挥官。敌舰正以极快的速度驶离，长官。
Sub-Commander. The enemy vessel is moving away at extreme speed, sir.
通知所有船只。武器官，
Alert all vessels. Weapons officer,
将主炮台对准企业号。
bring main batteries to bear on the Enterprise.
保持在曲速 9，长官。
Holding at warp 9, sir.
斯科提，打开那个设备的开关。
Scotty, throw the switch on that device.
试过了，长官。它不管用。
I did, sir. It's not working.
我本会称赞你能走到这一步，舰长。
I would give you credit, captain, for getting this far.
但你马上就要死了
But you will be dead in a moment
称赞是不必要的。
and the credit would be gratuitous.
上尉，打开通往罗慕伦飞船的频道。。
Lieutenant, open a channel to the Romulan vessel.
乌乎拉：是的，长官。
UHURA: Aye, sir.
我接通了副指挥官塔尔，长官。
I have Sub-Commander Tal, sir.
建立双向可视通讯。
Establish two-way visual contact.
我们有你在我们的武器下。你无法逃脱。
We have you under our weapons. You cannot escape.
这是柯克舰长。停火。
This is Captain Kirk. Hold your fire.
- 我们有你的指挥官在船上。 - 指挥官。
- We have your Commander aboard. - Commander.
摧毁这艘船。我给你下了直接命令，塔尔。
Destroy this vessel. I gave you a direct command, Tal.
舵手，侧翼速度。武器官，
Helmsman, flank speed. Weapons officer,
准备发射主炮，一旦我们达到最佳射击距离。
stand by to fire main batteries as soon as we reach optimum range.
- 斯科提，我们的时间不多了。 - 舰长，我正在尽可能快地工作。
- Scotty, we're running out of time. - Captain, I'm working as fast as I can.
你看，舰长，你的努力白费了。
You see, captain, your effort has been wasted.
史波克先生，离罗慕伦飞船的距离？
Mr. Spock, distance from the Romulan vessel?
十五万公里，舰长，接近地非常快。
One hundred fifty thousand kilometers, captain, and closing very rapidly.
准备，相位炮。
Stand by, phasers.
指挥官，请原谅我的反抗。
Commander, you'll forgive me if I put up a fight.
当然，这是意料之中的。
Of course, it's expected.
十万公里。他们应该开始向我们开火
One-hundred thousand kilometers. They should commence firing at us
在接下来的 12.7 秒内。
within the next 12.7 seconds.
- 斯科提。 - 现在准备好了，舰长，
- Scotty. - It's ready now, captain,
但我不知道我们的电路是否可以应付这个外星装置。
but I don't know whether our circuits can handle this alien contraption.
- 打开开关。 - 它可能会超载。
- Throw the switch. - It'll likely overload.
打开开关。
Throw the switch.
武器官，开始--
Weapons officer, commence fi--
消失了。他们有隐形装置。
Gone. They have the cloaking device.
快。根据最后的位置计算敌人的路线并开火。
Quickly. Compute enemy course from last position and open fire.
- 是的，长官。 - 苏鲁，转向 318 标记 7。
- Yes, sir. - Sulu, come about 318 mark 7.
318标记 7，长官。执行中。
Three-one-eight mark 7, sir. Executing.
隐形装置工作正常。
The cloaking device is working perfectly.
指挥官告诉我
And the commander has informed me
即使是罗慕伦人的传感器也无法跟踪如此装备的船只。
that even the Romulans' sensors cannot track a vessel so equipped.
谢谢你，史波克先生。
Thank you, Mr. Spock.
取消红色警报。
Cancel red alert.
我们会让你在最近的联邦前哨站下船。
We'll let you off at the nearest Federation outpost.
你很慷慨，舰长。
You are very generous, captain.
如果我可以被带到你的禁闭室，
If I may be taken to your brig,
我将作为你的俘虏。
I will take my place as your prisoner.
史波克先生将有幸护送你到你的住所。
Mr. Spock will have the honor of escorting you to your quarters.
舰长。
Captain.
指挥官。
Commander.
2号甲板。
Deck 2.
很遗憾你成为了一个不情愿的乘客。
It is regrettable that you were made an unwilling passenger.
这不是故意的。
It was not intentional.
联邦想要的只是隐形装置。
All the Federation wanted was the cloaking device.
联邦？
The Federation?
你想要什么？
And what did you want?
当我登上你的船时，那是我唯一的关注点。
It was my only interest when I boarded your vessel.
这就是你离开的全部原因。
And that's exactly all you came away with.
你低估了自己，指挥官。
You underestimate yourself, commander.
你会意识到很快
You realize that very soon
我们就会破解你偷来的隐形装置。
we will learn to penetrate the cloaking device you stole.
很明显。
Obviously.
军事机密是最短暂的。
Military secrets are the most fleeting of all.
我希望你我交换的东西更永久。
I hope that you and I exchanged something more permanent.
[开门]
[DOORS OPEN]
这是你的选择。
It was your choice.
这是唯一可能的选择。
It was the only choice possible.
你不会尊重任何其他人。
You would not respect any other.
这将是我们的秘密。
It will be our secret.
进入中立区，舰长。
Entering neutral zone, captain.
很好，契科夫先生。谢谢你，莱斯利先生。
Very good, Mr. Chekov. Thank you, Mr. Leslie.
麦考伊 [通过对讲机]：医务室呼叫舰桥。
McCOY [OVER INTERCOM]: Sickbay to bridge.
怎么了，老骨头？
What is it, Bones?
如果所有的争吵都结束了,
If all the shouting's over up there,
我想让你到医务室报告。
I'd like for you to report to Sickbay.
- 做什么的？ - 你该做手术了。
- What for? - Well, you're due in surgery.
我要恢复你的耳朵。
I'm going to bob your ears.
舰长，请你离开。
Captain, please go.
不知何故，它们在人类身上看起来并不美观。
Somehow, they do not look aesthetically agreeable on humans.
嗯，你来了吗，吉姆？还是你想一辈子
Well, are you coming, Jim? Or do you want to go through life
看起来像你的大副吗？
looking like your first officer?
我来了。
I'm on my way.